I realized why Ononoki-chan had always called me with such a weird nickname
Why did she call me 'oni no onii-chan',
as in devilish-onii-chan
The reason was very clear in the mirror world
Reason being that, I really was a devil, from being a vampire before
Even if the term isn't very respectful
It is the truth
Hachikuji-oneesan and Kushinawa-san both looked at me in the same way
Though, if vampires did not exist in this world
Vampires' traits should not exist either
Therefore, this theory would not work
Knowing I am a victim of a vampire
But not acknowledging
the existence of vampires
Truly is contradiction.
The truth is, vampires
indeed are non-existent in this world
There is no reason to call me 'oni no onii-chan'
But vampires not existing
Does not equate to Oshino Shinobu not existing too
The iron-blooded, hot-blooded, cold-blooded vampire
Oddity-killer, Kiss-Shot Acerola-Orion Heart-Under-Blade
The vampire that was once a human
Six hundred years ago
She was a human
Aristocratic
Making the castle her own
Living inside it as a princess
And that is her inner world
Oshino Shinobu's opposite-
Please don't be nervous
Please lift up your head
Araragi-sama
What is this...
There wasn't a vampire
on the other side of the curtains
Instead was an atmosphere created by only the noblest
By reflex, I knelt down
Please forgive me for
speaking with the curtain between us
Forgive me for not showing
my face whilst conversing with you
I have heard that you came
from another world. Is that right?
The Araragi-sama that came from another world
In other words, the person that was familiar with me
Is the same as you, but at the same time, not the same
Is that correct?
That's... right...
The Araragi Koyomi of this world gets to be called as 'Araragi-sama'?
Always wanting to take off Ononoki-chan's panties
Pestering Oikura
I can't figure out my character at all.
Is it really my reverse?
Shouldn't it be Ougi-chan?
It's an honour to converse with a human from another world.
Originally I was hoping to
drink tea and share thoughts with you
But there isn't any time left.
Araragi-sama
The situation you're in right now
Please explain it in a way I would understand.
To you, I am untrustworthy,
and we do not know each other
However, do open up
Even though I cannot guarantee your return
I can at least help in some way.
Ok...
Thank you so much.
You came from an interesting world
From your perspective
everything must look fake right?
On the other hand... for me to be a vampire...
I would love to try it out.
But for me, that is fake.
We probably think that the other party is fake.
Reminiscent of the moon
reflecting off the water's surface.
Unfortunately,
I am not the same as the me in the other world.
As the human counterpart
I do not have the power of
opening up a portal to the other world.
How awe-inspiring.
For Her Majesty to respond with such words
I should be ashamed of myself.
I should take on the
responsibility, and cut my own throat!
What am I thinking...
Why do I feel the absolute need to cut my own throat?
But, I think I can help you to devise a plan.
Just take it as some mere
rambling from an inexperienced person.
But please do hear me out.
I can't thank you enough.
Heart-Under-Blade.
It might seem that
devilish-oniichan can bear with it currently
He is indeed running out of
time, please do make haste.
I understand, Ononoki.
Araragi-sama.
I believe that it is in best interest
for you to return to your own world.
Only have I heard the words 'time is running out'
Her Majesty had pin-pointed
the exact thought in my mind.
To think our thoughts are now identical
How superfluous is the honour
that I have been bestowed upon.
No... I am so foolish to have
inferred, what Her Majesty was pondering on...
How grand would the punishment be!
But why am I thinking in this way?!
In other words, because you exist in this world
You will influence this world greatly.
Influence... Having a 'bad' influence
would be a better way of putting it.
I know that it is disrespectful to say this
However, Araragi-sama.
You are likened to a great disaster to such a fragile world.
From my perspective
It seemed like it was me
that was drawn into a disaster instead.
Suddenly Oshino Meme's words came to mind.
'Your victimized look really pisses me off.'
That is what he would say on a number of occasions.
Whenever something would happen,
I'd shift the problems onto apparitions
Shifting the responsibility away from myself.
That's what that specialist hated.
I never had those intentions
But again I adopted
the similar thinking as I had done in the past.
That was what Her Majesty was trying to point out.
How should I give my gratitude!
The world that you see as fake
Filled with contradiction and illogicality.
Has also balanced itself with its existence.
And you are shaking the balance.
Ononoki may look normal to you
However for us, her personality dramatically mutated.
To be truthful, I am starting to be influenced also
Who was the Araragi-sama I had been so familiar with?
My memories are starting to blur.
I...
How did I behave in this world?
Anymore carelessness...
and I would need to take my own life.
Guilt is slowly tormenting me.
Sorry but I cannot tell you that.
I-is it...
Because you have forgotten it and cannot recall?
That is not it, it has not got to that point yet.
Though if we continue like this, it may become reality.
Ononoki, you should not say anything extra.
Of course. I have not said anything.
Ononoki-chan had lied through her teeth.
Didn't you tell me that I stole your panties?
Or was that all a joke?
If that's the case, isn't that distasteful?
Well, it's not that her jokes are going too far...
B-but... I want to go back as soon as possible
That is what I want...
But like I said
I have no way of doing so.
Even if I got anywhere near
to my only hope which is Kanbaru's large bath
I am still not one hundred percent
sure if I can get in contact
with the other world.
That's right! If I were to burden
Her Majesty with such petty problems
The better option were to kill myself!
So again, why do I want to kill myself so bad!
That's it Shinobu, we've ran out of time.
Time is up.
I will take him back.
So, to conclude
How can you talk to Her Majesty like this?!
For Her to forgive, I'll use my death as...
No... I had stood up without Her Majesty's permission.
This slave will have to carry even more sins!
Die... Die... I must DIE!
I understand.
I will leave it to you Ononoki.
No problem, I am used to it.
Araragi-sama.
The path you are taking is indeed correct
However, this isn't enough
Do not think you can do it by yourself.
Do acquire help from others.
Just like how you gave me hope
Let us wish for someone
in this world to grant you hope too.
Unlimited Rulebook.
Talking to Her Majesty
for long periods of time brings danger.
To put it simply:
Being under Her powerful
charisma for too long makes you suicidal.
She did mention
'Time is running out' - and so on.
Wanting to die from being influenced by Her...
It's true that I accidentally knelt down
But having such a presence, is no laughing matter...
I assume that's why she stayed behind the curtains?
Correct, if you saw her beauty with your own eyes
Devilish-onii-chan
You would probably gauge your own intestines out.
Why would I choose such a painful way to die?
At least let me die less painfully.
Was Shinobu like this when she was human?
The Genuine Princess, Her Majesty.
To be honest, I don't think it was like that
If we use your theory
She would only be like that in Her inner world
And not actually in reality.
She also mentioned that it is similar
to the moon reflecting off the water's surface.
Well, Shinobu's influence
may have been too strong for this world.
It is quite clear why She was living by Herself.
The almighty presence She has. makes people suicidal
And that could easily be led to a revolution.
Being a human, but exhibiting what a human can not do.
Uhm, what did she say...
The path that I'm walking on is correct.
In other words, to pursue for
Kanbaru's bath as the way of returning to my world...
Is the right idea?
That's about right.
But she did say you would have to find helpers
Being alone would not get you anywhere.
Even so
I can't go back to ask Her what she really meant right?
Mhm, your suicidal points
have rised significantly, near breaking point.
Until those points
have dropped, it is safer to not go back.
What the hell are suicidal points?
It puts me on edge...
Even using a relaxed tone to explain it...
Though it's true that we have
no time to wait for the points to decrease.
Helpers, huh...
To intrude onto
Kanbaru's property, we would need something
That would attract Kanbaru's attention.
Something like that sounds impossible to find...
Ononoki-chan
Got anything in mind?
What kind of character could stop the Rainy Devil?
Good thinking, hmm....
Possessing such destructive power and fighting prowess
Also knowing the situation we're in,
Acknowledging how devilish-onii-chan is feeling,
Having great crisis awareness,
With the motivation to solve any problems,
To have on board professional knowledge,
Lastly, to be able to escape from any situation...
Is there anyone like this?
THAT'S YOU!
Koyomi!
The sun's rising!
Get up you lazy sleepyhead!
Alright, I'm changing, get out!
Or do you want to see me change?
Koyomi is lewd as ever!
But if it's Koyomi, it's fine
Take a look!
Don't d-do that idiot...
Disgusting...
What Shinobu said about my bad influence
By living together, in the same room
To think in terms of numbers,
Oikura spent the most time with me
I might have influenced her the most.
Ah, nii-chan, good morning!
We're going out to play with Sodachi-chan!
Is that so? Then have fun with her.
What do you mean...
Nii-chan what are you to Sodachi-chan?
See you later...
Ara, nii-sama, hope you are full of joy
Joy what?
Hmm? Brushing your teeth?
Nope, washing my face.
I get it, I get it, no need to say more.
Onii-chan wants her
cute imouto to wash his face for him right?
Then prepare yourself!
Prepare what?!
I am washing my own face.
Is it not okay if I do it?
Since when did we progress into a shoujo manga setting?
And why am I the female protagonist?!
I'm coming up!
Let's get you clean as a whistle.
Onii-chan you're in the way!
Onii-chan. Use your mouth
to fetch the soap from the soap box.
Then put it in my hand.
Why should I get the soap for you
while getting accused of being in the way...
And with my mouth?!
Close your eyes
Otherwise you might go blind
There's definitely that risk
when you used an excess amount of soap!
But why give such dangerous
warnings when you're just washing my face?!
I have to, this is my first time washing someone else's face.
My point is that, I may accidentally
pierce your pupils with my fingernail.
If it's warnings like that, its too late to tell me it now!
Eat my bubbles!
Hmm, this isn't good enough
Should I use Sodachi-chan's
face wash without her permission?
Let's not do that-
Ah yes, let's finish it here for today.
Let's splash the face a little
I am not taking fault for that!
I did warn you
Why didn't you do as said?
Eh? Is that so?
Anyways the water was gone,
there's nothing you could do about it.
Doesn't seem problematic either
Don't be too conscious of it-
Wait-
That is actually quite important
The portal to the other world
doesn't have to be in monkey-onee-chan's house.
It's actually in the sink of our house.
Don't say 'our house' so casually.
I'll tell Sodachi onee-chan what you just said
Please don't.
Don't bully Oikura into a corner.
But to be fair it was only for a moment
Maybe I was seeing things
I couldn't recreate what happened
I have no clue as why it would appear either.
Well the first time was the mirror
Second: the mirroring water
They happened in the same place.
The meaning of it is different though.
The similarity was that you were washing your face
That could be the condition for the portal to appear
What kind of condition is that?
I could wash my face when I'm showering...
Anyways, how ever you look at it
The reflected 'me' was
either laughing or not coordinating with me
But it didn't seem like important details.
If we had the same objective
The other me could call for
Shinobu or get someone that could to contact her
Hmmph, that is true
Then it looks like today's mission would be important.
Hopefully it'll be solved today.
I did spend a day unwillingly...
Oikura is starting to show some bad signs too.
Onii-chan
That change could be reverted with a simple method.
Have you noticed?
A simple method?
Yep, extremely simple.
What is it?
Could say it is a variant
of the Copenhagen Interpretation.
'Copenhagen Interpretation'?
Didn't you say it was simple?
What was it again, Quantum Mechanics?
Awkward.
I meant "Copernicus' Revolvement".
TL Note: コパルニクスの転回 (Copernicus' Revolvement) can be used to exemplify the way of dealing with things from a totally different perspective.
Who the hell knows?!
Don't get something so similar wrong!
In my opinion, even though Copernicus' Revolvement
and the Copenhagen Interpretation are very far apart
We could say this is a case of Copernicus' Revolvement.
If onii-chan gives up on returning to the original world
Then there wouldn't be any problem staying here forever.
I see!
There's that plan too!
You're so clever, Ononoki-chan!
Looks like there's no need for us to intrude Kanbaru's bath!
...Wait, in what way could this solve the problem?
If I continue to stay in this world...
That's because you've decided to return
In other words, onii-chan didn't intend to be here forever.
Like a transfer student that
uses their local dialect to boast about their homeland
Worsening the atmosphere in class.
What kind of example is this? Makes me feel uneasy.
If onii-chan gives up on
going back, also opening up to this world
Onii-chan will be influenced by this world
Be pressured-
Then onii-chan will revert to what he was before.
Though strictly speaking, it'll be a compromise
For us it'll seem that you are the same as you always were
Monkey-onee-chan won't attack you
As long as you don't get near her house.
If you made your mind up
You can start living a sweet life with Sodachi-onee-chan.
Don't say it like that's my ultimate goal
Like I'm staying in this world...
Just because I wanted a sweet, lovely life with Oikura!
Well, I guess it is a plan to consider.
For Ononoki-chan to have
come up with this plan, I'll apologize...
Because to live in this world
I will have to leave a lot of
things behind in the world I came from
If I still have hope, I will still pursue.
Even if I have to risk my life.
But I will have to risk my life too
W-well...
That's alright, I'm dead anyways
I'm just mentioning it. Just asking that's all.
It's not like the plan is flawless or anything
If devilish-onii-chan did get used to the status quo
What will happen if the real Araragi Koyomi came?
The real one?
I guess for the people in this world it'll be the real me.
But don't label me like some fake counterfeit!
Two of the same person that existed
Doppelgänger.
It'll destroy the balance of the world for sure.
So where did Araragi Koyomi really disappear off to?
Did he really switch places with onii-chan?
We're here
So as planned
I will try to buy some time
You can explore around the house a bit
Even bathe a little if you want onii-chan.
How can I be that relaxed now?!
There will be plenty of time
If it's me, not only 5 minutes
Even 5 hours is fine for me.
If I bathed for that long I'd pass out!
Go ahead devilish-onii-chan.
Unlimited Rulebook.
There isn't any significant reflection off the water.
Ah I remember
The reflection shows who
your significant other will be in the future.
It will show when you are bathing.
This feels great...
Not great at all!
Huh, who are you?
To ask for someone's name,
Why don't you say your own first?
I am Gaen Tooe.
So, who are you?
If you don't answer, I'll cut your dick off.